nodestorm: a live canvas your agent draws on while you decide
Claude Code (any MCP agent) proposes an architecture...
Components become cards, dependencies become edges
Status rails: existing, proposed - and the agent is now waiting on YOU
Every open choice is pinned to its component
Hover an option - the components it would ripple into light up
Picked - with the trade-offs recorded
Deciding the last open choice delivers automatically - watch the agent react
Notes ride along too - type a message and Send delivers it to the waiting agent
The canvas is yours too - add your own components
Rename, connect, delete - your edits flow back to the agent
Deleting an agent's component asks the agent politely
Undo covers every edit until decisions are delivered
The minimap pans big graphs - groups collapse into one card
Search highlights matches...
...and Enter zoom-cycles through them
Sessions are parallel brainstorms - agents can wait on one while you work in another
Compare shows how two sessions drifted
The timeline is the session's full decision log
Export writes a Markdown decision record - pros, cons, and the trail
Twelve palettes, light and dark, live-switching
Narrow window? The bar folds - message the agent from the compose pod
Even tiny windows keep every control reachable via More